出租
Taxi!
能麻煩你載我去這里嗎
Can you take me here, please?
對  查爾斯  不好意思
Right, Charles, sorry about that.
我給你講講我們的進展
OK, let me fill you in on where we are.
我們在行李箱里裝了可卡因
We had the cocaine in a holdall.
然后到了停車場
We moved into the car park
看見斯科特先生拿著桿雙管獵槍
where we saw our friend Mr Scott walking out
從他的車后面走出來
from behind his van holding a double-barrelled shotgun.
好  聽著  大概一個小時以后見
OK, listen, see you in about an hour.
好好  再見
OK. OK, bye.
不好意思  我是律師
Sorry about that. I'm a lawyer.
真的
Honestly.
這是杰米的爸爸伯頓先生
Jamie's dad, Mr Burton,
他今天來給大家講講他的工作
has come in today to talk about what he does at work.
-嗨  -你們知道律師干什么嗎  杰米
- Hi. - Do any of you know what a barrister does? Yes, Jamie?
-他讓人不用坐牢  -怎么做到的呢
- He stops people from going to prison. - And how does he do that?
他告訴法庭這個人沒罪
He tells a court that someone didn't do a crime.
有時候證據不足
And sometimes the evidence doesn't cut it.
然后他說好了放假回來卻不能回來
And sometimes that means he can't come on holiday like he promised.
其實我大部分時間都在庭上對法官講話
Actually, my job is mostly standing up and talking to a judge in court.
你都說些什么
What do you talk about?
如果有人說看見你偷了同學的筆
If someone said they saw you take your classmate's pen,
而你說你沒偷
and you said you didn't take it,
我的職責就是證明目擊者看錯了
my job would be to show that whoever saw you was mistaken.
要是我真的偷了筆呢
What happens if I did take the pen anyway?
那你就有罪
Well, then you'd be guilty.
對  但如果我說我沒偷
Yeah, but what if I said I didn't take it,
而看見我偷的人眼神又不好呢
and the person who saw me has bad eyesight,
而你嘴皮子很厲害
and you're so good at arguing
他們也不能確定是我偷了呢
they can't be sure it was me who took it?
這樣啊  那就叫合理懷疑
Ah! Well, then, that's what you call a reasonable doubt.
那我能把筆留著了
So I get to keep the pen?
對  那是你僥幸脫罪
Yes, but then you'd be getting away with it.
如果你爸爸站我這邊的話
Only if your dad was on my side.
bei1中央刑事法庭
-你好  查爾斯  -威爾
- Hi, Charles. - Will.
準備好了嗎
Are we ready?
皇家檢察署來電
Crown called.
瑪吉·加德納將是首席庭審律師
Seems Maggie Gardner's stepping in as lead junior.
又是她
Again?
她居然上電視之余還能接手案子
Surprised she could squeeze in a case between TV appearances.
看來是我的榮幸
Suppose I'm flattered.
你們可是針鋒相對  法庭應該賣票
It's like a derby match with you. They should sell tickets.
庫馬因先生手邊就這把刀
It was the only object Mr Kumarin had to hand.
獵刀不是防衛性武器
A hunting knife is not a defensive weapon!
聽名字就知道
The clue is in the name.
-加德納女士  -抱歉  法官閣下
- Miss Gardner. - I apologise, My Lord.
即將受到襲擊的人不需許可即能自衛
A man about to be attacked does not have to wait for permission.
法律明文規定  適當情況下
The law tells us that in the right circumstances,
先發制人保護自己是完全合乎情理的
a pre-emptive strike is entirely justified.
在此案中  有人用上膛的獵槍指著他的腦袋
In this case, a loaded shotgun aimed squarely at his head!
多虧斯科特先生準頭太差
We only have Mr Scott's appalling aim to thank
庫馬因先生今天才能坐在這里
that Mr Kumarin is sitting here today
而不是被人從夜總會的墻上刮下來
and not being scraped off the nightclub wall with a trowel.
好樣的  威爾
Well done, Will.
威爾先生  非常感謝
Mr Will, thank you very much.
-不客氣  -謝謝
- Pleasure. - Thank you.
保重
Take care.
"警方在對桑德拉·馬倫遭受兇殘謀殺
"Police continue to make headway again
一案的調查中又取得了新的進展
in their investigation into the brutal murder of Sandra Mullen,
近日發現的新證據起到了很大作用
acting on new evidence that has come to light in the past few days.
但警探依然請求目擊證人
Detectives however are still calling for witnesses to come forward
站出來提供有關馬倫女士
with any additional information they may have
遭受宗教式殺害的信息
concerning the ritualistic slaying of Miss Mullen,
馬倫女士被害時年25歲  是醫學院學生
whose tortured body was found on heathland by a dog walker last October.
尸體于去年十月在石南原被一名遛狗者發現
Miss Mullen, who was 25 at the time of her death
最后一次有人見到馬倫女士
and studying to be a doctor, was last seen leaving a night club
是她于周四凌晨離開夜總會"
in the early hours of Thursday morning."
不用了  謝謝  我們有保溫層
No, thank you, we have insulation!
我們有搜查令  要搜查此地房屋
We have a warrant to conduct a search of these premises!
早飯以后再來
Come back after breakfast!
福伊爾先生
Mr Foyle!
早飯以后再來
After breakfast!!
-表現很好  -謝謝
- Well-played. - Thank you.
-過得怎么樣  -痛并快樂著
- How's life? - Ah, pleasure and pain.
大話女人  英國ITV電臺午間談話采訪類節目
噢  凱特那天在《大話女人》上看到你了
Oh, Kate saw you on Loose Women the other day.
-你倒是挺冷靜的  -什么冷靜
- You're playing it very cool. - Cool?
就是排行榜這瞎扯淡的玩意兒
This... This whole Top 40 nonsense.
-你在說什么  -你沒聽說嗎
- What are you talking about? - You haven't heard?
你就裝謙虛吧
Oh, false modesty!
這很沒意思  威爾
It's so unappealing, Will.
我不知道你在說什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
咱們事務所還沒人當過第一名
We've never had a number one.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
你已經聽說了
You'd heard already?
沒  怪不得我在更衣室外被調戲
Er, no, but that explains the warm welcome outside the robing room.
不光是被調戲那么簡單呢
I don't think it's limited to there.
好樣的  伯頓先生
Well done, Mr Burton.
現在能當皇家法律顧問了吧
That's silk now for you, surely?
你說就是吧  蒙克先生
If you say so, Mr Monk.
你填申請  我給你買郵票怎么樣
You fill out the application, I'll buy a stamp. How's that?
別再調戲我啦
Don't do this to me!
你應該考慮下
You should consider it.
總不能一輩子當出庭律師吧
Don't stay a junior all your life, hm?
哈里斯可以  但那對你來說是紅磚大學
Well, Harris can, but that's red brick education for you.
紅磚大學  以英格蘭六大重要工業城市命名的英國著名大學
我喜歡弄臟手
I like getting my hands dirty.
你與眾不同  威爾  你很特別
Ah, but you're different, Will. So very... special.
瑪吉·加德納
bei1第二名
額外獎勵  伯頓先生
Bonus prize Mr Burton.
不行  我們周末要去小屋度假呢
No, we're actually up to the cottage for the weekend.
看一下吧  威爾
Read that, will you, Will?
要不了你多長時間
Knowing you it shouldn't take long.
搞不好那里沒有手機信號
Possible we're out of mobile range up there right now.
太不幸了  簡直悲劇
So very unfortunate. Tragic, in fact.
希姆金斯·布朗欽點了你
Simkins Brown asked for you. Personally.
-是嗎  -換做我是你
- Really? - Although I'd keep that
這種似是而非的事就不會到處去說
particular factoid to yourself if I were you.
他們沒選皇家律師  選了你
They asked for you over any of the silks.
也難怪他們
Can't say I blame them.
如果我是他們的委托人
If I was in their client's shoes,
肯定也希望找你這樣的常勝將軍
I'd want your record on my side.
如果你被鎖在鯊魚缸底下的保險箱里
If you're chained up in this safe at the bottom of a shark tank,
你肯定不會找保羅·丹尼爾斯
you don't call for Paul Daniels.
保羅·丹尼爾斯  英國魔術師  電視演員
肯定找霍迪尼
You call for Houdini.
霍迪尼  被稱為"現代魔術之父"  擅長逃生術
沖啊
Come on.
很好  過得好  加油
Nice one. Good pass. Good pass! Come on!
這樣才對嘛
There we go, now we're talking.
加油  注意看球
Come on. Keep an eye on the ball!
走起  搞什么  裁判
Off we go. Here we... Oh, come on, Referee!
天哪  能有點種嘛
Grow a sac, for God's sake!
-土豆  她是說種土豆  -你來了
- Potatoes, obviously she means sack of potatoes. - You're here!
-天哪  -射門  快射門
- Oh, God... - Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
小家伙
Oh, wee man.
我今早在外套口袋里發現了一個蘋果
I found an apple in my jacket this morning.
我借助水果給你傳遞信息
I was sending you a message -through the medium of fruit.
-什么信息  -吃水果
- The message being? - Eat fruit.
-你覺得我營養攝入不均衡嗎  -是的
- You don't think I'm getting my five a day? - No.
你就光吃奶酪
I don't think you're eating anything that isn't made entirely from cheese.
你得先按下按鈕吧
I think you'll find you have to press the button first.
我按了  就是按下去這個動作
I did press it. I used a pressing motion.
現在好了
There now.
-我剛剛就是這么做的  -行吧
- I just did that. - OK.
謝謝你的支持  太感謝了
Thanks for your support. Really appreciate it.
好了  出發啦
Come on, we're going.
等等
Hang on.
把你的包從后座拿下來  好嗎
Get your bags off the back seat. OK?
-本  -你們好啊
- Hey, Ben. - All right.
你是洗泡泡浴的花衣魔笛手
You're the Pied Piper of bubble baths.
花衣魔笛手  德國童話中的人物
這里也許還能擠進來一個高大的蘇格蘭人
You know, there might be room in here for a large Scotsman.
-我還有點事  -隨便你吧
- I've got to catch up on something. - Oh, well, suit yourself.
可惜了這兒朦朧的燭光
It's all candles and twilight in here though.
是你的損失哦
Your loss.
別打呼了
Stop snoring.
抱歉  害你睡不著嗎
Sorry, am I keeping you up?
真幽默
Funny guy.
杰米說你昨天在學校帥呆了
You were quite the hit at school yesterday. So Jamie said.
他們貌似挺喜歡
They seemed to enjoy it.
他的小伙伴們都想讓你做他們的律師了
All his wee pals want you to be their lawyer now.
知道有你撐腰  他們都要有恃無恐
They're all going to go out and commit GBH safe
去犯重罪了
in the knowledge you'll get them off.
還真讓人寬心啊
Well, that's very reassuring.
可他們不知道你的大腦里滿是洞洞
Little do they know that that large brain of yours is full of holes.
你的硬盤滿了
Your hard drive's full.
-這就是你的問題  -我明白了
- That's your problem. - I see.
你需要時不時做個備份
You just need to back it up now and again.
要怎么做呢
How do I do that?
你身上又暖又舒服
You're so nice and warm.
希姆金斯先生  為什么選我去打官司
Mr Simkins, why did you choose me to lead this?
而不選皇家律師呢
I mean, why me, over a silk?
因為我見過太多皇家律師瀟灑地接手
Because I've seen too many silks who try and waltz in
草率地應對一樁案子
and blunderbuss their way through a case
他們只在出庭的路上瞥一眼而已
they've only glanced at on the way to the court.
因為像這樣的案子  我想要
Because in a case like this I want someone
一個整天埋頭研究證據的人
who spends days elbows deep in the evidence.
因為我的委托人如今正站在一塊石頭
Because my client stands between a rock
和一大坨屎中間
and a bucket of shit
他需要盡可能多的幫助
and he needs all the help he can get.
還有呢
And?
-說實話  -是的
- Honestly? - Yeah.
因為你總能贏
Because you win.
你現在睡這里了嗎  伯頓先生
Are you sleeping here now, Mr Burton?
-現在什么時候了  -周二
- What time is it? - Tuesday.
我愛上卡洛斯·特維斯了[阿根廷球員]
I think I fancy Carlos Tevez.
他是隊長
For captain.
你看過這些照片嗎
Did you look at these pictures?
以前見過這樣的情況嗎
You ever seen anything like it? Before?
我從沒見過
I've never.
大多時候她都沒斷氣
She was alive for most of it, you know?
活著呢
She was alive.
我們步行穿過公園
"We were walking through the park,
聽著iPod里面的音樂
and listening to music on our iPod.
回家以后才發現鞋底有血跡
We did not notice the blood on our shoes until we got home."
我們沒注意走過了哪些地方
Because we'd not been paying much attention to where we'd been walking,
我們走到了
and because our walk had taken us through
灌木深處  以及很深的草叢中
areas of deeper undergrowth and high grasses.
第一眼看到這血  我們以為
When we first saw the blood we presumed
誤踩了動物尸體
we had stepped in the remains of an animal."
-比方說  一只松鼠  -沒錯
- A squirrel, for example? - Yes.
知道嗎  灰松鼠正在殺紅松鼠
Did you know the grey squirrels are killing all the red squirrels?
-有耳聞  -可他們最近又發現一種黑松鼠
- I did, yes. - But now they've discovered a black squirrel.
-福伊爾先生  -它們又在殺灰松鼠
- Mr Foyle. - And that's killing all the greys.
早晚會知道  小心沒大錯
Goes to show, you can't be too careful.
福伊爾先生  可以開始了嗎
Mr Foyle. Can we please get on?
福伊爾先生  你通常哪天去洗衣房洗衣
What day do you take your laundry to be service washed, Mr Foyle?
-周二是洗衣日  -能不能解釋
- Tuesday's wash day. - Can you explain why,
數月來一直周二洗衣的你
after months of Tuesdays,
為何突然周一去洗衣
you took your washing in on a Monday?
褲子不夠穿了  不是嗎
We'd run out of pants, hadn't we?
因為沒有干凈衣服可穿
We took our laundry to be washed a day early
所以提前一天去洗
because we'd run out of clothing.
-是的  -鞋子上的血跡讓你更加迫切地
- Correct. - The fact we found blood on our shoes after our walk
-想要提前去洗衣  -事實如此
- increased our desire to do our washing early. - That's the truth.
你的鞋子一般都用洗衣機洗嗎
Do you normally wash your shoes in the washing machine?
沾了血的話就用
I do if they have blood on them.
好
Right.
我們必須要談一下網站的事情
We're going to have to talk about the websites.
對方會試圖指控
The other side are going to try to claim
你習慣性地瀏覽通常被稱為
you habitually view images and video
"極端色情"的圖片和視頻
that are commonly referred to as "extreme pornography",
"極端色情"包含
an umbrellaterm for filmed acts
危及或狀似危及人身生命
which threaten, or appear to threaten, a person's life,
造成參與者嚴重傷害
result in serious injury to participants
或者有毆打  啃噬
or appear to involve torture, biting,
針對人類尸體的性行為等內容
sexual interference with a human corpse.
這與被害者遭受的傷害
And that this has a link to the nature of the injuries
構成一定的聯系
sustained by the victim.
我不做那種事情
I don't do that kind of thing.
很遺憾  你的信用卡記錄顯示的恰恰相反
Unfortunately, your credit card statements tell a different story.
你在數家網站都有消費記錄
They show payments to a number of websites,
這些網站被曝光含有
which have been revealed to distribute this...
這種類型的內容
this kind of material.
信用卡撒謊
The credit cards are lying.
好吧
Right.
我必須告訴你  福伊爾先生  形勢很嚴峻
I have to tell you, Mr Foyle, already this is a huge challenge.
你陳述的方式需要仔細琢磨
We're going to have to work on your presentation style.
你所見都是事實
What you see is what you get.
沒錯  現在這正是問題所在  不是嗎
Yes, well, that's part of the problem, isn't it?
-他一定要在這里嗎  -是的  必須
- Does he have to be here? - Yes, he does. Yeah.
是這樣的  伯頓先生
Here's the thing, Mr Burton,
不知道你有沒有注意到
and I don't know whether you've picked it up
或者你的第六感有沒有發覺
or perhaps your sixth sense might have spotted it.
我不是特別喜歡人
I don't like people very much.
我就不是那么和善的一個
I'm just not a very nice person.
-我不是來評判你的  -對  歸紅衣服做
- I'm not here to judge you. - No, the man in red does that.
我來是為你辯護  盡我所能陳述你的案件
I'm here to defend you and present your case as best as I can.
-為此...  -你認為是我做的  對吧
- In order to do that... - You think I did it, don't you?
這就是問題所在
That's the problem here.
我沒這么說
It's not what I was saying.
你認為我對那可憐的女人做了那些可怕的事
You think I did all those awfulthings to that poor woman.
-福伊爾先生  請聽我說  -我想我不會
- Mr. Foyle, please listen to me. - I don't think I will.
福伊爾先生
Mr Foyle.
我要他出去
I want him gone.
他是你的事務律師
He's your solicitor.
出去
Gone.
他讓我緊張
He was making me nervous.
要休息一下嗎
Do you want to take a minute?
瞪著我
Staring at me.
-福伊爾先生  -看著我的眼睛
- Mr Foyle. - Look me in the eye.
可以繼續了嗎
Shall we get on?
要不要來杯熱茶
How about a nice cup of tea?
福伊爾先生  我是你的辯護律師
Mr Foyle, I'm your defence barrister.
如果你以任何形式私下向我承認有罪
If you privately confessed your guilt to me in any way
但公開堅稱無罪
but publicly maintained your innocence,
我馬上跟著希姆金斯先生出去
I'd be following Mr Simkins there,
并且離開時鼓勵你承認有罪
and I would have encouraged you as I left to enter a guilty plea.
我沒有罪
I'm not guilty.
那么我們可以開始了
Then this is where we are.
你干得很不錯
Well, good job you're here then.
-令人振奮  -但愿如此
- Refreshing. - Let's hope so.
你做事的方式
Your manners.
-倒滿  -一點點就好
- Full? - Just a splash.
知道嗎  說來有趣
You know, it's funny.
和你相處越久
The more time we spend together,
就越覺得我們相似
the more you remind me of me.
好吧
Right.
-伯頓先生  -等一下
- Mr Burton? - Give me a minute.
-你沒事吧  -只是需要透透氣
- Are you all right? - I just need some air.
-麻煩給我一包萬寶路  -好
- Can I have 20 Marlboro Lights, please? - Yep.
-有的話再來一只打火機  -有
- And a lighter if you have got one. - Sure.
她來了  哈洛街57號升起的新星
Ah, here she is, the rising star at 57 Harlow Street.
瑪吉  我知道我應該無條件支持你
Now then, Maggie, I know I should really be rooting for you
可是你該明白
without exception, but you should know
第二也沒什么丟人的  你看巴茲·奧爾德林
there is no ignominy in coming second. Just ask Buzz Aldrin.
我要求重新計票
Well, I demand a recount.
-仿佛回到了律師學院辯論決賽  -是嗎
- Takes me back to Middle Temple Moot Finals. - Really?
是的  你和我  幾乎一模一樣
Yeah, you and me. Almost an exact replay.
那是很久以前的事情了
It was a long time ago.
聽說利亞姆·福伊爾的案子是你對我們朱利安
I heard you're up against our boy Julian on this Liam Foyle malarkey.
-是嗎  我們的朱利安  -是  很意外
- Is that so? Our boy? - Yes. Surprised it's not
對手竟然不是你  還真有點不習慣
you on the other side. Seem to be making a habit out of it.
我這不是給你機會挑戰下別人嗎
Thought I'd give you a go against someone else for a change.
-差不多了吧  -不嫌多
- Had enough, eh? - Never.
我在想是不是多做做辯護
I am just thinking of transitioning into more defence work.
-失陪了  -好的
- Excuse me. - Sure.
福伊爾這個案子對我來說太"猶大"了
Anyway, this Foyle case is a little too St Jude for my liking.
他是敗局的守護神
He's the patron saint of lost causes.
是嗎  我還不知道
Oh, I didn't know that.
好吧
Right, well,
-我再去找點酒來  -好的  謝謝
- I'll go and get us some more rubbing alcohol. - Great, thank you.
我是認真的  我看過案情摘要
I'm serious. I've seen the brief.
-你為什么接這個案子  -我是律師
- Why are you doing? - I'm practising law.
拜托  這根本是收拾不干凈的爛攤子
Oh, come on. It's almost a no-questions jobbie.
你就是想增加曝光度吧
It might be exposure for all the wrong reasons.
我才不是為了曝光度  瑪吉
I don't do things for exposure, Maggie.
那為什么接
Why do you do it?
因為每個人都有權申辯
Because everyone deserves a defence.
吹蠟燭吧
There you go.
-許愿吧  -老媽不要再煩我了  -沒錯
- Make a wish. - I wish my mum would stop annoying me. - Yes.
-誰要吃蛋糕  -我
- Who wants a piece of cake? - Me!
-真的嗎  -要吃  要吃
- Are you sure? - Yes! Yes! Yes!
好吧  你是說還要繼續調查嗎
OK, so you're saying there's more to find?
好的  能把一切都記錄在案嗎
Yeah. And would you go on record with that?
很好  好的  明天我讓事務所的人聯系你
Great. Great, OK. Someone from my office will call you tomorrow
我們約個時間
and set up an appointment.
謝謝  明天見  再見
Thanks. Thank you. Speak soon. Bye-bye.
-他是誰  -懂電腦的聰明人
- Who was that? - That's a clever man who knows about computers.
幫你備份大腦嗎
Is he going to back up your brain?
不是  工作上的事
No, it was for my work.
-他能幫你勝訴嗎  -但愿吧
- Will he help you win the case? - I hope so.
他們來了
Oh, here they come.
-凱特和孩子都好嗎  -很好  謝謝
- How's Kate and the family? - Very well, thank you.
瑪吉今天應該會來旁聽
I think Maggie's in the gallery today.
-為什么  -掂量掂量對手的能耐吧
- Why's she doing that? - Checking out the competition I expect.
當第一名就要有覺悟  威爾
That's the trouble with being number one, Will.
人人都想把你拉下馬來
Everyone wants to knock you off your perch.
我聽說你上周申請了延期審理
Now I heard you asked for an adjournment last week.
-是的  -遇到麻煩了嗎
- I did indeed. - Trouble at mill?
也不是  就是需要更多時間
Not really. Just needed more time.
怕是沒時間了  咱們都來了
Well, here we are, I'm afraid.
沒錯  都來了
Here we are indeed.
我真是喜歡你鐵面無私的表情  老兄
I must say, I do like your game face, old boy.
還沒到那個時候呢  兄弟
You haven't seen it yet, old boy.
有的罪行惡劣到無以言述
Some crimes defy description.
那是對文明一詞的玷污
They debase our so-called civilisation
公然挑釁人性的底線
and defy every boundary of humanity left to us.
殺害桑德拉·馬林斯的人
Now the person who took the life of Sandra Mullins
只能被稱作卑劣的施虐狂
can only be described as a malignant sadist,
他這種行徑是蓄意傷害  恐嚇
who did so with the intent to traumatise, to terrorise,
給予受害者非人的痛苦與折磨
and to inflict the maximum amount of pain and suffering.
控方力在證明  毫無疑問
And we intend to prove, without doubt,
這個人就是利亞姆·福伊爾
that that person was Liam Foyle.
脖子周圍有嚴重的瘀傷
Severe bruising around her neck,
甲狀軟骨和舌骨嚴重骨折
her thyroid cartilage and hyoid bone were badly fractured.
死因是勒殺
Cause of death was strangulation.
另外還有性侵犯
Other injuries were sexual in nature,
體內體外均造成傷害
internal and external,
未發現雙眼眼球
both eyes were missing,
是在死前或者更早時被強行取出的
removed with force close to the time of death, possibly before.
公園的植被覆蓋到了東北角
The park gets overgrown towards the north eastern corner.
有很深的草叢  山楂  薰衣草和蕁麻
Long grass, hawthorn, lavender, nettle beds.
你早上經過時發現了什么異樣嗎
And did you see anything unusual on your morning route?
我看到一個男人
I saw a man.
原本躺著  后來起身了
Getting up from a lying position.
休斯先生  依你的職業素養
Mr Hughes, in your professional capacity,
你能確認面前的這份信用卡交易記錄
can you please confirm the credit card statements before you
準確說明了這些交易是由你的銀行
are an accurate reflection of payments made by your bank
代表賬戶所有者利亞姆·福伊爾先生做的嗎
on behalf of the account holder, Mr Liam Foyle?
是的
Yes.
此卡的這些交易
And these payments were made by the card
都是在今年前三個月進行的  對嗎
over the first three months of this year, is that correct?
對
Yes.
并且都是網上在線
And they were all made online to companies
與亞洲和歐洲的公司交易
across Asia and Europe,
這些公司都傳播和制作相同的產品
all of which distribute and produce the same... product,
也就是淫穢作品  對吧
namely pornography, is that correct?
據我們所知是這樣的
Yes, that is our understanding.
休斯先生  大部分網站
Mr Hughes, many of these sites,
我們為了進行調查
and I'm afraid we have had to visit them
必須對其進行訪問
in the course of this investigation,
發現它們都含有極度惡劣的行為
have shown acts of extreme depravity
根據我們對法醫報告的研究
which, we understand from the forensic reports,
發現其與桑德拉·馬林斯被謀殺前
show disturbingly accurate similarities to the injuries
所受的傷害驚人的一致
that befell Sandra Mullins before she was murdered.
這里我特指身上的咬痕
I talk specifically in relation to the bite marks
-還有對生殖器的損毀  -胡說
- and the mutilation of genitalia. - Liar!
福伊爾先生  我只給你這一次機會
Mr Foyle! You have one chance with me, and that was it.
再違反秩序就算作藐視法庭
Any more from you and I shall hold you in contempt.
-殺人犯  -請安靜
- Murderer! - Silence, please!
休斯先生  請回答問題
Mr Hughes, please answer the question.
沒錯  是這張信用卡
Yes, it is the same card.
謝謝  沒有要問的了  法官大人
Thank you. No further questions, my Lord.
bei1暴民
伯頓先生
Mr Burton?
法官閣下  在庭審之前
My Lord, before this trial began
我提交過延期審理的書面申請
I made a written application for an adjournment.
鑒于現在缺少專家證詞
I'm asking you now to reconsider that
我希望您能重新考慮下那份申請
application in the light of the gravity of the expert testimony.
-拜托  -伯頓先生
- Oh, come on. - Mr. Burton.
你的請求非常不合時宜
This is most inappropriate.
我認為這期間能發現更多關鍵證據
I submit an adjournment will bring vital evidence to light.
雙方都可以讓專家參與
Let both sides have their expert,
再由陪審團做最終判斷
and let the jury decide.
伯頓先生
Mr Burton,
公眾對這起案件極為關注
there is huge public interest in having
希望能盡快進行審判
this case heard as soon as possible.
你的專家
The fact your expert
未能完成查驗證據的工作
has not mustered himself to the task at hand
本庭對此并不關心
is neither here nor there.
不是他效率低
He's not slow,
他正在收集可能的新證據
it's that he's gathering potentially new evidence.
那是同一臺電腦
It's the same computer.
雙方請的都是電腦取證的專家
Both of your experts are computer forensic specialists.
我不認為兩個訓練有素的人
I can hardly see how two trained men
檢查同一臺電腦
looking at the same equipment
會得出截然不同的結論
could produce so radically different conclusions
并對審判結果產生影響
that it would make a difference.
恐怕這是不可能的
I'm afraid it simply isn't on.
如果法官閣下能再仔細考慮...
I think if My Lord could look a little closer...
你的申請被拒了  這個決定不會更改
Your application was refused and it shall stay refused.
我不會因藐視法庭而處罰你
I will decline from pursuing you on contempt
但這是給你的最后一次警告
but let this be your last and final warning.
現在是午餐時間  暫時休庭
We'll break for lunch now.
木已成舟  伯頓先生
But the train is on the tracks, Mr Burton.
為了你的委托人著想
And for the sake of your client
你還是隨機應變為好
I suggest you deal with it.
-明白  法官閣下  -起立
- My Lord. - All rise.
威爾
Will?
你要睡會兒覺
You should try and sleep.
-我沒事  -我說真的
- I'm fine. - I mean it.
你認為自己戰無不勝  但其實不是這樣
You think you're invincible, and you're not.
我們應該給這些窗戶換鎖
We should get new locks on these windows.
你聽到我的話了嗎
Were you even listening to me?
換成帶鑰匙的框架鎖
Frame locks, with keys.
我的天  接下來的兩個月
Oh, God. You're going to drive me crazy
你是要把我逼瘋嗎
for the next two months now, aren't you?
我的一位同事剛為一個十二歲男孩辯護
A colleague of mine just defended a 12-year-old boy
他把下水道清洗劑
who poured drain cleaner
灌進了好朋友的喉嚨
down the throat of his best mate
就因為他朋友不讓他用自己的手機玩游戲
because he wouldn't let him play a game on his phone.
什么世道
The world is broken.
你不該在睡覺前看恐怖電影的
You shouldn't watch scary movies so close to bedtime.
是啊
Yeah.
你的表現可沒給我什么信心  威爾
Not inspiring much confidence up there, Will.
我知道我在做什么  福伊爾先生
I know what I'm doing, Mr. Foyle.
我在那兒可沒看到
Not from where I'm sitting.
-那就解雇我  -為什么我要那么做
- So sack me. - Why would I want to do that?
你說呢
You tell me.
只要我受雇于你  就為你工作
I work for you as long as you'll have me.
我道歉  威爾  我知道你在盡力幫我
I apologise, Will. I know you've got my back.
很感謝你對我坦誠相待
I appreciate your honesty very much.
我們繼續吧
Shall we get on?
-你只有一臺電腦  對嗎  -沒錯
- You only have one computer, is that correct? - Yes.
但我不明白這與那女人的遭遇
But I don't see what that's got to do with
有什么關系
what happened to that woman.
你會明白的
You will.
必須有人為桑德拉·馬林斯的死付出代價
Someone must pay for what happened to Sandra Mullins.
我們面臨的是人性危機
Our very humanity is at stake,
正如我這位淵博的同行所說
as my learned friend has indicated.
如果利亞姆·福伊爾有罪的話
It would be convenient for everyone here today
對今天在座的人而言是順理成章的
if Liam Foyle was guilty.
戴上手銬后  他將永不能翻身
The cuffs go on and he's gone forever.
看上去似乎是鐵證如山
The evidence seems overwhelming.
但事實并非如此
But it is not.
可能福伊爾先生并不招人喜歡
We may dislike Mr. Foyle.
如果我們看到他走過來  可能都要繞道走
We might cross the street if we saw him coming.
但為他辯護并不需要喜歡他
But we do not have to like him to defend him.
因為這里并不是比人氣
Because this is not a popularity contest,
也不是搞政治迫害
this is not a witch-hunt,
這里是法庭
this is a court of law,
在這個國度  當你被指控犯罪時
and in this country, when you're accused of a crime
在最終被證明有罪前  都假定你是無辜的
you are presumed to be innocent until proven guilty.
毫無疑問  我這位淵博的同行
And make no mistake, not a shred of what you've heard from
為檢方說的每一句話
my learned friend acting for the Prosecution
都是無憑無據的
has given any proof at all.
所展示的是不可靠的證人證詞
I will show you unreliable witnesses,
懶惰無能的法醫鑒定
lazy forensic science,
以及情感訴求  而不是事實真相
emotional appeals instead of factual accuracies.
就是如此  還妄自斷言我的委托人
Oh, yes, and the casual assertion that my client is
是極端色情片的消費者
a consumer of extreme pornography.
首先  我們來談談這一點
First, I think, we will talk about that.
我的專業是電腦取證和數據分析
I am an expert in forensic computer data analysis.
克羅博士  你檢查過福伊爾先生的
Dr. Crowe, have you had a chance to examine the hard drive of
電腦硬盤嗎
the computer belonging to Mr. Foyle?
檢查過
Yes, I have.
你是按照這起案件的
And you did this instructed by
檢察官的指示去做的  對嗎
the Prosecution in this case, is that correct?
是的
Yes.
遺憾的是  為辯方
And unfortunately Dr. Weeks, the gentleman
檢查電腦的威克斯博士
who has helped examine the computer for the Defence
還沒能完成他的工作
has not yet finished his work.
不過他把到目前為止的記錄給了我
However, he has passed me his notes to date
我想就此對你提幾個問題
and I'd like to ask you questions about them.
不論你使用電腦上過什么網站
Wherever you go on the internet, using a computer,
都會留下痕跡
you leave footprints.
-對嗎  -沒錯
- Is that correct? - Yes, it is.
即便把文件刪除了
Even if you've deleted a file,
像你這樣的專家還是能找出痕跡
someone like you is able to see it.
-通常是如此  -你到底想問什么
- Most of the time. - Where is this going?
在我的專家缺席的情況下  法官閣下
And in the absence of my own expert, My Lord,
我這位淵博的同行友好地
my learned friend has kindly
提供檢方的專家來參與審理此案
tendered the Prosecution expert on this matter.
我請求跟他探討一下這一點
I beg some time to explore this point with him.
好吧
Very well.
我淵博的同行斷言我的委托人
My learned friend alleges that my client paid for and viewed,
經常購買和觀看
on a regular basis,
大量不堪入目的圖片  包括
numerous depraved and abusive images, including...
"折磨  損毀  勒殺和奸尸的行為"
"Acts of torture, mutilation, strangulation, and necrophilia."
在你對他的電腦的分析中
Um, in your analysis of his computer,
你有否證實福伊爾先生
did you establish that Mr Foyle
確實訪問過那些圖片
had actually visited any of those websites that
所屬的網站嗎
pertained to those images?
-沒有  但他的信用卡賬單  -謝謝
- No, but his credit card bills... - Thank you.
我淵博的同行聲稱我的委托人用信用卡
And my learned friend asserted that my client paid for access
購買了那些網站的訪問權限
to many of those websites with his credit card.
那么
Now,
如果他沒有訪問這些網站  為什么要付錢呢
why would he pay for them if he didn't actually visit them?
這話說起來不中聽
It may sound reprehensible
但他付的錢沒有得到回報  不是嗎
but he's not getting his money's worth, is he?
如果他不訪問那些網站
How did he pay for access
那又是如何購買權限的呢
to those sites without actually visiting them?
在他的上網記錄中  他向許多色情網站
Many porn sites were on his internet history
提供了信用卡的信息
to which he submitted his credit card details.
這樣他就能得到一個解鎖其他內容的密碼
That's how he received a password to unlock other content elsewhere.
他的信用卡信息有沒有可能是偽造的呢
Is it possible that his card details were falsified at that point?
你是什么意思
How do you mean?
就是當他向成人網站提供信息時
That when he submitted his details to the adult site,
它們被
they were taken
未知的第三方盜取和利用
and used by unknown third parties
并用來購買和解鎖你所說的"其他內容"
to pay for and unlock this "other content" as you call it.
-有那種可能嗎  -我覺得有吧  有
- Is that possible? - I suppose so, yes.
考慮到這種可能性  如果我們能證明
So given this possibility, if we were to prove, in this court,
真的發生了信息偽造  那福伊爾先生
that such falsification occurred, would Mr Foyle be shown to be,
是不是就成了身份欺詐的受害者
in fact, a victim of identity fraud?
這不是有關極端色情的庭審
This is not a trial about extreme pornography,
而是審理令人發指的謀殺...
this is about the horrific murder...
我們的專家本來在證實其中的聯系
Our expert was in the process of proving this link.
因此我們所提出的延期申請被駁回了
Hence our application for an adjournment, which was refused.
我淵博的同行提出了一系列
My learned friend brought these hideous
聳人聽聞的主張  而我再次申請延期
allegations to bear on this case and I reiterate my request.
專家證詞對雙方都有影響
The expert testimony cuts both ways.
庭警  請帶陪審團離開
Usher, please excuse the jury.
剛剛出現了程序問題
A matter of procedure has just arisen,
我需要跟兩方都談一談
I need to talk to both sides about it.
我們很快就會叫你們回來
We will call you back presently.
去我的辦公室
My room, I think.
法官
Judge.
我的委托人被皇家檢察院
My client has been falsely
錯誤地戴上了極端色情愛好者的帽子
branded an extreme porn enthusiast by the Crown,
此事已經泄露到網絡社交媒體上
this has now leaked online to social media,
平面媒體也趁勢加以報道
where it's been duly picked up by the print media,
給我的委托人貼上了
which has now tainted my client
虐待狂  變態和戀尸癖的標簽
with the label torturer, pervert, necrophiliac,
所以這個陪審團必須解散
so much so this jury must be discharged
重新召集  即使有報道限制
and a new jury called. Even with the reporting restrictions,
考慮到本案已經產生的新聞
given the press this case has already generated,
福伊爾先生也得不到公正的審判
Mr Foyle cannot be given a fair trial.
-我申請停止起訴  -太荒唐了
- The inevitable application is to stay the indictment. - This is absurd.
我此時請求是恰當的
I made the request in good time.
-是  我知道  -陪審團對被告的偏見
- Yes, I know. - The prejudice to the accused
在我看來是永久性的
in the eyes of this jury is, in my view, permanent.
我雖不情愿  但這種情況下除了批準申請
Reluctantly, I feel that I have little option in these circumstances
-我別無選擇  -法官  拜托
- but to accede to your application. - Judge, please.
我沒有辦法  朱利安
I ballsed up, Julian.
抱歉  我們去結束這件事吧
I'm sorry. Let's get this over with.
所以  最終結果是  我別無選擇
And so, as a result, I have no alternative
只能解散陪審團并釋放被告
but to discharge the jury and release the defendant.
全體起立
All rise.
你應該感到羞愧
You should be ashamed of yourself!
-恭喜  干得好  -那是個漏洞
- Congratulations, well done. - It was a mistake.
我只是確保他們付出代價
I just made sure they paid for it.
威爾  好樣的
Will, good man.
-這是我的工作  -謝謝你  我的朋友
- Just doing my job. - Thank you, my friend.
不客氣  保重
Pleasure. Take care.
-再教我一次  -你自己來
- So show me again. - You do it.
好吧  但是別看著我
OK. But don't watch me,
你看著我就弄不好  我鴨梨山大
I can't do it if you watch. I'm like a kettle.
你鴨梨山大是什么意思
What do you mean you're like a kettle?
-弄好了我再告訴你  去吧  -好吧
- If I get this right I'll tell you. Go on. - OK.
"買衣服的時候要用  想要"
"When buying clothing to say what you want, use... Gostaria."
-想要  -"我想要一件襯衫"
- Gostaria. - "I'd like a shirt. Gostaria uma camisa."
我想要一件襯衫
Gostaria uma camisa.
"我想要一條褲子  你想要一條褲子嗎"
"I'd like a pair of trousers. Gostaria umas calcas."
什么
What?
"要合適的尺碼
"To get the right size,
用下面的短語  我是40號"
use the following phrases. I am a size 40."
"我是40號"
"O meu numero e quarenta."
我是4...40號
O meu numero e qua... quarenta.
"如果他們沒有合適的顏色
"If they don't have the right colour,
要同樣款式的藍色就這樣說
here is how to ask for the same thing in blue.
這個有藍色的嗎"
Do you have this in blue?"
你在沖誰揮手
Who are you waving at?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不知道是什么意思
What do you mean you don't know?
那個男人  是他開始揮手的
That man. He just started waving.
什么男人
What man?
他已經走了
He's gone now.
-進去就是了  -你在尿尿嗎
- Just go in. - Are you peeing?
你說呢  聽著  深呼吸  推開門
Possibly. Listen, just take a deep breath and open the door,
別扭扭捏捏的
you big Jessie.
我做不到  我有點怕
I can't. I'm scared.
-不就是次聚會嗎  -詹妮說她會來
- It's just a reunion. - Jenny said she'd be here.
-我又忘了她是誰來著  -呵呵
- Who was she again? - Funny.
你們總該有些共同點吧
At least you'll have something in common.
我們說好的  現在哪兒都找不見她
We had a deal. I can't see her anywhere.
沒事的
You'll be fine.
我應付不來這些人  他們都太...
No, not these people. These people are all so...
-嗨  -你好啊  見到你真好
- Hi. - Hi, great to see you.
-兩面三刀  -這么和你說吧
- Two-faced. - I'll tell you what.
如果你到上奶酪的時候還心慌氣短
If you're still hyperventilating by the cheese course,
你大可來找我們啊  你知道我們在哪兒的
you can always come and see us. You know where we are.
我們永遠歡迎你
And we're always pleased to see you.
行  謝了
OK. Thanks.
我該掛了  拜
I'd better go. Bye.
-媽媽  -什么事
- Mum. - Yes?
你笑什么呢
What you smiling at?
這是意外之喜
It's a surprise.
好大一個驚喜
A nice surprise.
過來  你想問什么
Come here. What's with the questions?
-看你  你總是...  -松手
- You, you're always... - Get off.
-愛丁堡怎么樣現在  -還那么瘋
- So how's Edinburgh? - Still mad.
不過你還是該回來
You should come back though.
你會有套好房子  孩子的教育也更好
You get a nicer house, better schools.
你有沒有考慮過換工作
Are you considering a career change?
我現在挺好的  多謝關心
I'm doing OK, thanks.
我知道  我看報紙了
I know. I read the papers.
讓他們等我回來再開始  好嗎
Don't let them start without me, OK?
可冬天來臨的時候  他...
And still, when winter came, he...
[拉丁語禱詞]
阿門
Amen.
喂
Hi.
你去哪兒了  我打了好多電話
Where were you? I've been trying for ages.
-發生什么了  -天啊  先前有人在外面
- What's happened? - God, there was a man outside.
我不清楚  但知道有人在外面
I don't know, but there was somebody outside.
我們在小屋這邊
We are at the cottage.
-有人  什么人  -我不知道是誰
- Man?! What man? - I don't know what man it is!
-但肯定有個人  -凱特  深呼吸
-There was a man, somebody! - Kate. Kate. Breathe.
再說一遍
Tell me again.
他...他就在窗外  我當時在洗澡
He was... He was at the window, and I was in the bath...
我洗澡的時候他就一直看著我
He was looking in at me when I was in the bath.
他怎么可能在窗外呢
How could he be at the window?!
我也不知道  但他就在窗外
I don't know but he was at the window!
打電話報警  鎖好門窗  呆在臥室里
Call the police, lock the doors, stay in the bedroom.
聽到沒  不要出去
OK? Do not go outside.
我立馬趕回來  我愛你
I'll be there as soon as I can. I love you, OK?
聽到我說的了嗎  你電話打了嗎
Did you hear me? Are you calling them?
我在打
I'm c-calling.
長官
Guv!
bei1可惜你要走了
會不會是你之前的委托人表達什么觀點
Is it possible that one of your ex-clients has a point to prove?
可能你敗訴了  有過嗎
Someone you failed to defend, perhaps did some time?
沒有
Well,... no.
你聽上去很肯定啊
You sound very sure.
查爾默斯警探  伯頓先生從未輸過一場官司
Detective Chalmers, Mr.Burton has never lost a case.
你有沒有拒絕過誰的委托
Have you ever refused to represent someone?
-說實話我們沒那個權力  -怎么說
- We're not really allowed to do that. - Allowed?
挑揀案子是不允許的
Cherry-picking is frowned upon.
大家都餓了  你們都餓了
Everybody's hungry. Everybody's hungry.
大家都餓了
Everybody's hungry.
皇家法律顧問那邊有沒有消息
Any sign of a reply from the QC Selection Panel?
這個嘛  是這樣的
Yeah. Look, about that.
往后推一推可能比較好
You might want to delay a little.
-什么投訴  -違反職業道德
- What kind of complaint? - Unprofessional conduct.
他怎么沒先來找我們
He didn't come to us first?
看來他是想讓你更難受些
Looks like he wanted to cause you maximum discomfort.
直接找法律監察員和律師標準委員會  難辦
Went straight to the Legal Ombudsman and the BSB. Both barrels.
福伊爾先生聲稱
Mr.Foyle asserts that you
"根據第301條A1
"Engaged in conduct which is dishonest
你涉嫌非正當的或有損
or otherwise discreditable to a barrister contrary
出庭律師名譽的行為
to paragraph 301 A1,
尤其是你對他的辯詞的準確度和
in particular that you expressed doubts about
真實性表達了質疑"
the validity and honesty of his plea."
什么
What?
-這是真的嗎  -當然不是
- Is this true? - Of course not.
簡直是瘋了  我們贏下了這個案子  贏了
This is insane. We won the bloody case. We won!
似乎這還不夠
Looks like it's not enough.
他到底是在干什么
What the hell's he doing?
你提交的皇家法律顧問的申請
I'm afraid your silk application is going to have to wait
恐怕要等到此事解決后了
till this is all sorted out.
威爾  我很抱歉  太不走運了
I'm awfully sorry, Will, it's very bad luck.
我們要立馬處理這件事  扼殺在搖籃里
We need to weigh in on this right away, stop it in its tracks.
火力夠猛的話  應該能行
Enough firepower, it may well work.
丹尼
Danny!
看你還能找到誰回辦公室  行嗎
See who you can rope back into the office, will you?
這都六點了
It's six o'clock.
我們現在就研究如何處理  怎么樣
We'll thrash out a strategy here and now, all right?
工作上出了點事情  這事兒有點詭異
Yeah, there's been a bit of a thing at work. It's a bit weird.
我可能得晚點回了
I'm going to have to stay later
要不我們一起上去吧  你能等我嗎
but maybe we can all go up together? Can you hang on?
我們已經準備出發了  我們在上面等你好了
We're ready for the off. Why don't we just see you up there, eh?
不過你抓緊點  我有東西要給你看
But hurry up, OK? I want to show you something.
-這么神秘  -沒什么  對了...
- That's cryptic. - No, not really. Oh, and listen...
信號不好了
Oh, I am losing you.
-"喂"  -一會見  好嗎
- "Hello?" -Now, I'll see you later, OK?
-"喂  喂"  -掛了
- "Hello? Hello?" - OK.
-到了  到了  -我餓死了
- We are here. Yeah, we're here. - I am really hungry.
活該
I don't care.
聽著  我們要等你爸爸回來
Listen, we are going to wait for your dad to get back
然后一起吃飯  好嗎
so we can all eat together, OK?
"你好  我是凱特
"Hi, it's Kate,
現在不方便接電話  請留言  拜"
I'm not here right but leave a message. Bye."
杰米
Jamie?
"搞清楚是白天還是夜晚
"Try to find out if it is day or night.
-打招呼有哪兩種方式"  -"很高興..."
- What are two ways to greet someone?" - "Muito prazer..."
"早上好  下午好"
"Bom dia. Boa tarde."
"最近的藥店在哪里"
"Where is the nearest chemist?"
"藥店在哪里"
"Onde esta a farmacia?"
凱特
Kate?
Kate?!
凱特
"那兒有  那里  是的"
"There is. Ha, sim."
凱特
Kate?
Kate?!
杰米
Jamie?!
凱特
Kate?!
凱特  杰米
Kate?! Jamie?!
杰米  杰米
Jamie?! Jamie!!
杰米
Jamie!
天啊
Oh, Jesus!
凱特
Kate!
爸爸
Dad!
-杰米  杰米  -爸爸
- Jamie?! Jamie?! - DAD!
杰米
Jamie!
快啊
Come on!
是  報警  救護車
Yes! Police! Ambulance!
言語是蒼白的  威爾
Words are not enough, Will.
你需要休息多久都行
Take all the time you need.
錢伯斯律所是個大家庭
Chambers is a family.
家里人就應該相互照顧
Like all families we take care of one another.
這一原則我們將堅持到底
We will run with this right through to the end.
不惜一切代價
Whatever it takes.
-謝謝  -我說到做到
- Thank you. - You have my word on it.
我們一定會讓他伏法
We'll make sure we get him.
怎么樣了
How are things?
對不起  不該這么問
Sorry. Shit question.
我在努力
I'm getting through it.
抱歉這么突然給你打電話  我正好在附近
Sorry to call out of the blue, I was in the area.
很高興你打電話了  丹尼  我很感激
It's really great that you called, Danny. I really appreciate it.
-你一切都好嗎  -挺好
- How's everything with you? - Fine, fine.
我們正在...
Well, we're just...
全力以赴  打趴那個混賬
..Pulling out all the big guns. Going to blitz the bastard, yeah?
怎么了
What is it?
-我不知道要不要告訴你  -告訴我什么
- I don't know if I should tell you. - Tell me what?
利亞姆·福伊爾今天確定了辯護律師
Liam Foyle confirmed defence counsel today.
是誰
Who is it?
我以為你還在休假
I thought you were still on leave?
還在休
I am.
我給你寄了卡片  希望...
I, erm, I sent you a card. I hope...
你替他辯護
You're defending him.
如果你是說利亞姆·福伊爾  是的
If you mean Liam Foyle, then yes.
確實如此
Yes, you're correct.
聽著  那些事情發生后  我是說...
Look, after everything that's happened, I mean...
我知道你很難過  真的
I know this must be very hard for you. I really do.
是的
Yeah.
你跟我一樣清楚  無論好壞...
You know as well as I do, for good or bad...
怎么說呢
What can I say?
每個人都有權申辯
Everyone deserves a defence.
沒錯  瑪吉
That's right, Maggie.
沒錯
That's right.
福伊爾謀殺了桑德拉·馬林斯
Foyle murdered Sandra Mullins.
下集預告
-你要知道這一點  -庭上你不是這樣說的
- You need to know that. - You said otherwise in court.
你讓那人進來  你就危險了
Let that man in, you're risking everything.
我說真的  千萬別一個人
I mean it. Don't be alone.
是今天嗎  辯護
It was today, isn't it, the plea?
-他們應該給你打電話  -告訴我
- They should have called you. - Talk to me.
-其實他被保釋了  今早  -啥時候的事
- Actually he got bail. This morning. -Great. When was this? Ohh!
這些律師都沒什么仁慈之心
These lawyers don't have an ounce of mercy in them.
很好控制他們
They can be manipulative.
-還沒有跟你道謝  -不客氣
- Never said thank you. - Oh, you're welcome.
再見
See you soon.
你打算什么時候告訴我
When were you planning on telling me?
-我今晚要見所有人  -爸  小心
- I want a meeting with everyone tonight. Everyone. - Dad! Look out!
-他在這里嗎  -他們說他已經走了
- Is he here? - They said he'd already left.
-為什么不給我打電話  -爸爸
- Why didn't you call me? - Dad! Dad!
爸爸  爸爸
Dad! Dad!
shad2脫 罪 大 師
第一季  第一集
YYeTs人人影視英劇社傾情奉獻
bei1翻譯  DT的寵物熊貓  愛卿遛小鳥
bei1翻譯  Silmar  噎死青春
bei1翻譯  面條打包子  珞格格
bei1翻譯  妄想的絨布熊  泰斯
bei1時間軸  吉吉  今  獄
bei1特別鳴謝  POTO的小飯桶
bei1特效&后期   寶寶祝圣安村的大紳紳生日快樂
bei1總監   泰斯·雪諾